Nguyen Cong Trieu

Fullstack Web developer

Name Nguyên Công Triều Birth 28/06/1998

Phone +84 327673346 Email trieunguyen2806@gmail.com

Address 61/14 đường số 8, Trường Thọ,

TP.Thủ Đức, TP.HCM





As a programmer with more than 3 years of experience in developing websites, web applications, dynamic personality, always dedicated and responsible at work, always actively learning and completing the assigned work well.

Have a strong background in terms of UI building and API building, clean code. Experience in building and managing complex projects flexibly. I want to develop myself further to become a full-stack developer who can meet all needs, take on all challenges from the company and customers.

During my time in the previous workplace, I not only learned technical skills, but also knowledge in the field of e-commerce, logistics, always aiming to achieve the best user experience.

My goal: to become a better developer, will learn, research and hone strongly in front-end knowledge because I want to bring the best user experience. Besides, I still hone my back-end skills to get better and better and become the Technical Lead.



Work experience

3/2021 - 7/2021

Magento Developer

FPT Software (Viet Nam)

- Programmer for a major camera manufacturing company in the Japanese and American markets (Canon).
- From a Fresher I took on the position of developing categories and optimizing products.
- I had the opportunity to work with foreigners for the first time, improving my listening skills.

© fullstack.edu.vn

7/2021 - 4/2023

Full-stack Web Developer

FPT Software (Viet Nam)

Start working with my primary language – NodeJs, ReactJs.

Building a warehouse management system for nutrition supplier

3A Nutrition (Abbott) based on NodeJs (ReactJs & Nestjs).

I was assigned the main development task of Front-end, in charge of developing ReactJs for web applications, developing Single Page Application that integrates QR code scanning into the application to be able to scan codes and many other features. to be able to operate warehouse processes.

I was assigned the main development task of Front-end, in charge of developing ReactJs for web applications, developing Single Page Application that integrates QR code scanning into the application to be able to scan codes and many other features. to be able to operate warehouse processes.

5/2023 - Present

Full-stack Web Developer

Suzu Group

- I started working with a team of about 8 people, building a website for Loc Troi Group.
- I work as a Frontend, building user interfaces using Reactjs and Nextjs. Read design files from Figma
- After about 4 months, the team completed the website for Loc Troi Group, and I was able to
 participate in the project of building a social network for the company. This was the time when I
 learned quite a bit about how to deploy a project from Fontend to backend. I do full stack built
 on Turbo Repo architecture, using Reactjs and Nextjs languages, Tailwind CSS, postgresSQL,

• • •

Link website: https://dev.suzu.net



Education

2016/09 – 2020/09 Ton Duc Thang University

Major - Electronic communications



- Main
 HTML, CSS, Jquery, BootStrap, Figma, TailWind Css, Prisma, JavaScript (ReactJS: React-Hooks, React-Redux, ES6, Management State and Components, Global State, Context, ReactJs with Antd Design.)
 - · Node (NestJs, Reactjs, Nextjs)
 - RESTful API
 - MySQL, PostgreSQL, NoSQL (MongoDB basic)
 - Server (Apache, Nginx, Redis,...), Docker, DockerHub (basic)

Other • SVN, GIT, Jenkins, Jira

Elasticsearch



CANON

(03/2021 - 07/2021)

Client	US, JAPAN
Descriptions	Addressing a large number of customers who need to work on e-commerce sites, especially
	cameras.
Number of members	100
Position	Developer
Responsibilities	- Developer
	- Take the position of developing categories and optimizing for products.
Technology in use	- PHP

akaWMS

(07/2021 - 04/2023)

Client	Abbott Viet Nam
Descriptions	Building a warehouse management system for nutrition suppliers
	3A Nutrition (Abbott) based on NodeJs (ReactJs & Nestjs).
Number of members	7
Position	Developer
Responsibilities	- Developer main Front-end
	- Daily receive requirements directly from the client and fix it for the client to test.
	- Coordinate with BE, BA and Tester to solve the requirements from the client in the best way.
	- Develop new features according to client's request.
	- Offer a personalized solution to re-optimize the interface.
	- Optimize old features.
	- Besides, I also participate in building and developing APIs for the system using NestJs
	Framework with Microservice architecture based on the assignment and direction of Leader.
Technology in use	- Frontend: ReactJS
	+ Management State
	+ Management Components
	+ React-Hook, React-Redux
	- Backend: NestJs
	- Architecture: Microservice, Websocket, docker, Redis,

© fullstack.edu.vn

Loc Troi Group, Suzu Social Network

(05/2023 - Present)

Client	Loc Troi Group, Suzu
Descriptions	Build website for Loc Troi and.
	Build website social network for Suzu Based on design file using figma.
Number of members	8
Position	Developer - Frontend
Responsibilities	Code FE for website Loc Troi Group: Provides full UI features, clean code and high user experience. Code Full stack for website Suzu Social Network: Build full stack website using Turbe Bone.
	• Code Full-stack for website Suzu Social Network: Build full stack website using Turbo Repo and nextjs, tailwind css, postgreSQLDivide components appropriately for high inheritance.
Technology in use	 Frontend: HTML, CSS3, React-Hook, React-Context, State, Context API, Tailwind CSS, Backend: Nexjs
	Database: PostgreSQL

© fullstack.edu.vn